Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
The bloodshed should stop
in Bithynia, Osman Bey.
I want an everlasting peace.
Can I come in my Bey?
Come in, Boran.
The Catalan has spoken, my Bey.
They took orders from Michael Kosses.
Michael Kosses.
Let's take a tour.
Sure.
You are pretty, Masha Allah (praise be)
So, don't you have a Bey, a husband?
No.
I haven't found someone for me yet.
Of course you can't, girl.
Unbelievers are useless.
We can find you a valiant from Kayi , ha?
You see the situation, Michael Kosses.
They ambushed us
on our way back from Sogut.
Some run away.
Some fell down.
Only this one left in our hands.
Their aim...
was to abduct my guest Priest Gregor.
Is Priest Gregor with you, Osman Bey?
I'm surprised.
I didn't know it.
Sir, are you fine?
Don't worry Andreas.
I am fine.
Your wound must be treated
as soon as possible.
It can't wait any longer.
I asked him who he works for.
Maybe you want to hear too.
We attacked you
with the order of Lord Kosses.
This is a cheap trick, Osman Bey.
Apparently, someone is...
...trying to put the blame on me.
Look at him!
If he was one of my men...
he wouldn't be in this situation.
Also I would have already
taken Priest Gregor.
Either Rogatus or someone else
is trying to offload the blame.
Do not let them trick you, Osman Bey.
Only Allah cannot be tricked, Kosses.
They may trick me.
Don't worry about me.
Don't, Osman Bey!
I have just learned that you have Gregor.
How can I have done this?
You are a wise man, Osman Bey.
Everyone in Bithynia tries to
trick each other.
You know it very well.
You are right, Kosses.
You Lords are expert at tricking people.
However...
if this dog is telling the truth...
you are going to pay for it dearly.
If I had known that you had Gregor...
...I would have done everything I could
so far, Osman Bey.
They tried to trick you and me,
both of us.
Do not let them trick you Osman Bey.
No matter how good the hunter is...
The wolf always finds a way out.
I am neither prey nor a hunter,
Osman Bey.
You should know that.
Excuse me.
You are excused, Kosses.
Just for now.
You are excused.
Malhun Hatun.
Mari liked Turkish rugs a lot.
Beyond just liking them.
I want to buy your rugs, if it's okay.
With pleasure.
We would be glad.
- Sir, are you okay?
- I am absolutely not!
- We are going back right now!
- Sure.
- Where are the horses?
- Back there, sir.
Hurry!
Ladies.
I am grateful to you
for this beautiful conversation.
Besides, I want you to know that I'm very
excited for the trade we're going to make.
The rugs will be ready, Mari.
We'd like to see you again.
Of course.
I loved it here.
I'll visit again.
You can come anytime.
Our doors are open to anyone.
Malhun Hatun...
I said to Mari that rugs would be ready,
but we lack rugs.
It's hard to deliver on time.
Don't worry, Bala Hatun, there are
Kizilbeyoglu tent's rugs.
If we still lack, we'll ask the
tents around.
Do you think we can make it on time?
Of course we will.
We are one.
You are right.
You are good at trading.
I think you are the one
to be responsible for this job.
We'll manage, Inshallah.
Thank you.
Brother, is there a problem?
We are leaving right now, Mari.
Osman Bey.
Your tent is as glamorous as you deserve.
Your ladies took care of me very well.
I am grateful.
I hope your brother is grateful too.
He has seen things that
he hasn't before.
You let Kosses go despite what
the Catalan said, Osman Bey.
I want to know, brother.
I want to know who is backstabbing whom.
They wanted to bait Rogatus.
Then Kosses.
They are setting a game again, my Bey.
They put the blame on each other.
I want to say that
"let them wear away each other" but...
What they do always end up
affecting us.
Wind can only remove the dust
from a rock.
So, the lords are scheming behind
each other...
If we use their weakness,
the conquests are soon, brother.
If our enemies are biting each other...
then, we'll hunt them!
İnegöl, Harmankaya, Bilecik...
maybe Bursa.
Why not?
You are right, my bey but--
Once we have all Turkmens
join our cause...
once sisters bring joy to our tribe,
and we assure our unity...
why not, Osman Bey?
If it wasn't for the dream of
our ancestors, why would we be here?
You are right.
But firstly, Kosses...
We'll watch him as a wolf watches
a sheep.
We'll watch him and
find out...
whom we will bite.
Brother, we need to find a way to
put a spy next to Kosses.
May I enter, my bey?
Come in.
My bey, you summoned me.
Release the Catalonian.
Release him but follow him.
Be his shadow.
You'll know every step he makes,
Cerkutay.
Once we find the moment, we'll
strike them like a lightning.
As you order, my bey.
We'll watch them like shadows
and hit them like lightning.
Göktuğ, the alps should
sharpen their swords.
They should get ready
for a campaign.
As you order my bey.
İnegöl Castle
Hey! Get up!
-Is he dead?
-I hope not.
If he is, Lord Nikola kills
us all.
My bey, Bala and I thought that we can't
prepare Mari's carpets in time.
If you allow us, we want to gather
women from Kızılbey and other tribes.
You thought well.
We need to finish it before winter.
It will relieve the folk as well.
My bey, may I enter?
Come.
My bey, Kutan is here.
He wishes to speak.
Let him in.
Osman Bey.
Our tribe...
Turgut Bey...
Nikola raided our tribe.
They showed no mercy
to the children and the women.
He burnt the tribe.
That vile man!
Kutan.
Raise your head.
What happened to Turgut Bey?
He imprisoned Turgut Bey.
We are without a head, Osman Bey.
That vile heathen!
Tell me, what does Turgut Bey have to
do with Nikola?
I don't know, Osman Bey.
I don't know.
That vile dog!
For all the Turks he made bleed,
I will rip his heart out.
Tell the people. I will save your bey
from that vile devil.
-Boran.
-My bey.
Go to Turgut Bey's tribe
with Kutan.
Have enough alps with you.
Do everything that needs to be done.
As you order, my bey.
May Allah bless you, Osman Bey.
May Allah bless you.
-Brother.
-My bey.
Now, go to Nikola and ask for Turgut Bey.
He'll either give us Turgut Bey,
or his head.
Either he'll give him, or I'll destroy
İnegöl to its last standing building.
Tell him there will be retaliation for
all the Turks that he made bleed.
Alright, my bey.
Bravo, Turgut Bey.
Bravo.
You didn't disappoint me.
What did I tell you, Argos.
All these Turks are the same.
They have stubbornness.
You can take their lives but not
their stubbornness.
Slowly, shepherd.
Slowly.
There is no need for wildness.
Don't worry,
I'll hand you over to your new
owner soon.
I won't kill you...
with that, but with
these hands.
My face will be the last face
you see in this world.
Impossible, Turgut Bey.
Impossible.
Soldiers,
Take him away.
Arbus.
This gift is your responsibility.
Have your eyes on him.
- Mistakes... I don't...
- You don't like mistakes.
I don't.
Freaking shepherd.
You used to go yourself in such situations,
Osman Bey.
Now you are sending a messenger.
I am now Bey Osman.
I am Osman who spreads
the seeds of a state.
What makes me important...
What makes a Bey important is his alps...
His messengers...
His sisters...
...and his scholars.
I want to build a system.
A system that...
everyone can find peace in it.
Everyone including Muslims and non-Muslims
will want to be a part of it.
It must be ready by tomorrow.
It just needs a couple hand.
It'll be ready.
Lord Aya Nicola is waiting for you.
Gündüz Bey.
You honored us.
I like surprise guests.
Lord Nicola, you know why I am here.
It's Osman Bey's order.
We want Turgut Bey,
whom you keep as a captive.
What is your offer in return of such an
important thing, Gündüz Bey?
Nothing.
Osman Bey will take Turgut...
...And he'll give me nothing
in return, yes?
If you allow me.
I like my meat bloody.
Rare.
But every time, I get a wood-like
meat!
Wood!
As you see, Gündüz Bey.
You can't get everything you want.
Lord Aya Nikola!
This is important!
Turgut Bey is a Turkmen Bey. Osman Bey
would give his life but not him.
It's in our laws.
And be sure that we'll
obey that law.
Your law.
Your laws...
Gündüz Bey.
You consider yourself
to be the head of the Turkmens...
but you can't
protect any of them.
Turgut attacks my dear friend
Michael Kosses' sister...
and kidnap her.
Will it go unpunished?
Is that so?
I will make him pay for what
he did to Mari.
Nikola. I'm telling you
what Osman Bey says.
It's up to you to listen to him or not.
It's not up to me. If it was,
I still wouldn't give him.
Yes, I wouldn't.
I'll give him to Michael Kosses.
For Mari.
My lions! Come on!
Muslubeşe, your enemy raised
his sword.
Where is your shield?
Don't let your enemy get closer
than the length of your spear.
As you order, my bey.
Alps!
The enemy is out of control.
Dishonorable Nikola raided
Turgut Bey's tribe...
and imprisoned him.
Just when our pain was fresh
about our martyrs, we added new ones.
When a Turkmen tribe burns...
my heart burns.
It's the day of unity!
Gündüz Bey went to take Turgut Bey.
If he returns empty handed...
we'll crush down the walls
of Nikola upon him.
A Turk can never be a slave!
-Now equip your bloody weapons!
-As you order, my bey!
Harmankaya Castle
This Osman is still suspicious of me
about the alp issue.
So, Mari, your brother needs to
make better moves.
It's the thing you do the best, brother.
Most importantly, I need to
take Father Gregor...
from Osman's hands.
I can't keep the Emperor
waiting.
Osman is taking his steps carefully.
And he is determined.
It won't be easy to take Gregor.
Indeed.
Sir, news from Aya Nikola.
He said that he has Turgut.
-He'll send him to you tomorrow.
-Good.
Turgut is really important for Osman,
Mari.
For some reason, he sees himself
responsible of everyone.
Luck always sides with the powerful.
Indeed.
Actually...
he'll take Turgut and give Gregor.
-Your wound can't wait any longer.
-Nothing is more important than this...
including my life.
But if it goes like this, they'll notice
my wound soon.
He'll always be with us, Master Gregor.
I live to protect you.
I wish my death to be for the same cause.
We need to protect it well.
But how? We can't keep it on us.
They might search us.
We got a clue now.
Baysungur.
You stay here and watch them.
I will go and tell my bey.
Come on.
Bilecik Castle.
Lately, we meet a lot, Lord Rogatus.
Every time, your pursue gets
fatter.
-You can't complain about that.
-I'm not complaining.
Even though we couldn't get
Father Gregor, we were succesful.
God is giving us another chance.
Aya Nikola imprisoned a
Turkmen Bey named Turgut.
This Turgut is very important
for Osman.
-If we obtain him...
-It means that we have Father Gregor.
According to what I heard from
my spies in Nikola's castle...
Kosses will be going there personally
to take Turgut.
Take Father Gregor for granted,
Lord Rogatus.
Be careful.
He is a devil.
Anselmo is always careful
against all devils.
I'll bring Turgut to you,
don't doubt that.
-Nikola will give Turgut to Kosses.
-Why is that, brother?
He dotes upon Mari. He wants to
revenge her.
That dog Nikola...
Why is he doing that?
He wants to steal Mari's heart.
Mari is single, my bey.
Nikola wants to marry her...
and get her brother's support.
-Thank you.
Then, we need to do an ambush
to save Turgut Bey.
Nikola is getting prepared, Osman Bey.
They are preparing a cage for Turgut.
Soon, he'll give him to Kosses.
This is the end of the words.
Sharpen your swords.
For a single tear drop of a Turk...
we can burn the whole world.
My bey, what if it's all a trap?
They know that you won't
leave him behind.
What if they are trying
to lure you?
But even if it's a trap...
we need to find a way and
save Turgut Alp.
We can't have the other tribes' support
when he is imprisoned.
They should know that Osman Bey
won't leave anyone behind.
Of course.
-May I enter, my bey?
-Come in.
We found it, my bey.
We followed the wounded jackal and
it led us to it's den.
But no one came or left.
Baysungur is still watching it, my bey.
The wolf tasted blood.
We are following them.
We'll bite them soon.
But let's take care of this
Turgut issue first.
Then, we'll march against
the Katalonians.
We'll, my bey. We'll.
Brother, get ready for the ambush.
Alright, my bey.
Gonca, you are responsible for
the carpets.
Don't worry, Bala.
Gökçe, help Gonca Hatun.
Do as she says.
Gökçe, it's not a thing that
you can do.
Go and help the women out there.
I can take care of the carpets.
İnegöl Castle
Welcome!
Nikola!
Why did you come all this way?
I was going to send the gift
with soldiers.
I'm happy to see you, dear Mari.
The gift is so precious that I wanted
to come personally, Nikola.
True. You should've seen him...
when he was looking at his burned
tribe, Mari. This is nothing.
Oh, your present is coming.
Here is your present, dear Mari.
Look, dear Mari.
Look at your gift.
What did that wild wolf
turn into, right?
He is like a pet now.
Look how he sits...
calm and quiet.
Wild!
We should understand him. His tribe
burnt down.
His alps were murdered.
So, he suffered a lot, dear Mari.
A lot.
Right, Turgut Bey? Right?
It's good that I came personally,
Nikola.
-It's good.
-It's good, Kosses.
It's good.
Soldiers! Take him away.
I'm thankful, Aya Nikola.
Harmankaya's road divides
into two here.
The river here overflows
this time of the year.
I know it well. We rode a lot there.
But, so does Kosses.
So, he'll take this one.
Göktuğ, Cerkutay.
You'll go in front.
Saltuk, you'll attack from the
right flank.
Alright, my bey.
Keep your eyes open.
Mari, you better keep your
eyes on the road.
Do you think that Osman will
attack us, brother?
What do you think?
Anselmo...
Your man gives my name to Osman...
and you face me like an idiot. Did you
think there would be no consequences?
Lord Kosses.
This is all Rogatus' plans.
Rogatus bought my man.
You know, Catalonians like money.
I was also betrayed. I have nothing
to do with this.
Rogatus wants to use me
against you.
He offered me a lot of money
for Turgut.
-He'll set an ambush.
-Rogatus!
I need to make good decisions to not
end up like this, Lord Kosses.
How can I know that this is all...
not a part of a plan that you
made with Rogatus?
You know what you know, Lord Kosses.
To believe, you shouldn't know.
You don't have the numbers to fight with
Rogatus when he attacks you.
If you take the chance to
lose Turgut...
don't believe me.
Like Osman wasn't enough...
You will come to my ambush.
-Osman?
-Osman, of course!
Osman will surely make a move to
save Turgut.
We mostly fight for gold, Lord Kosses.
But there is something earned much
harder. It's trust.
What do you want, pretty Byzantinian?
Take your hand away!
Why are you doing this?
Why are you helping me?
Why?
Anselmo wants to gain trust, Lord Kosses.
You better use this chance well, Anselmo.
For your own good.
If we move the way you
were moving, we'll be on their lap.
Let's go this way.
No one uses this way because
of the risk of an overflow.
You know Bhytinia well.
You can't get away from Rogatus'
ambush in any other way.
Alright.
We'll listen to Anselmo's advice.
Come on!
Where are they.
-They aren't coming.
-They will. Be patient.
-They'll come.
-I can wait.
But these ones can't wait for them.
This silence isn't good.
It isn't.
No one is coming, my bey?
They'll come. Wait.
They'll come.
Alright, my bey.
My bey, the catalonians...
I was following them.
They united with Kosses' troops.
-Then?
-It was like they weren't expected.
Kosses' soldiers drew their swords,
then things calmed down. They united.
My bey,Anselmo and Kosses talked
for a while.
Then, they changed the road.
Alps!
My bey.
Get ready at once!
We'll stop them. Come on!
Lord Kosses.
Who is this Turgut?
Why does Osman want him? He must
be important.
He is not important. Just an ordinary
Turkish bey.
Osman and Turkic laws.
Who knows what non-sense
reasons he has.
What about you?
He is my enemy, Anselmo.
I think this explanation
is enough for you.
-What's this, Anselmo? Why did we stop?
-Lord Kosses.
I am taking Turgut, Lord Kosses.
You sold me out to Rogatus, didn't you?
Your loyalty is only to gold, right?
Let Turgut go, Kosses.
Let him go so that I spare your and your
beautiful sister's life.
I will never surrender.
I won't give you what you want!
And God is my witness I will kill you
myself!
Don't be stupid, Kosses!
All I want is Turgut!
Also, you were the one telling he was
worthless.
All right!
Turgut is yours.
Soldiers, let them take him.
Osman!
Osman Bey!
Take him down!
Come on, alps!
Mari!
Brother!
Mari, stay with me!
Stay behind me!
Damn it! Don't miss him!
Catch him!
Damn it!
Alps! Don't let them breathe!
Come on!
Brother!
Attack!
They only strengthen our anger by running.
What do we do now, my Bey?
We know where Turgut Bey is going.
Come on!
Oh no!
What am I going to tell Bala?
Hello, hatuns.
Gonca?
What happened here?
What happened to these?
What is this, hatuns?
Who would do this?
Tell me how this happened!
We don't know, Bala.
No one saw anything.
I ask you Gonca!
Didn't we trust you with them?
Didn't we tell you to look after the rugs?
Is this how you fulfill your duty?
My Bala, it happened overnight.
I--
I gave you a duty!
I didn't tell you to make excuses!
There is nothing to do anymore,
Bala Hatun.
Mistakes happen.
Is this a mistake to make, Mahur Hatun?
How will we make up for that many rugs?
We were barely making them.
Hatuns, separate the good ones.
Let's see how many are missing.
Let's see so that we can make up for them,
Bala Hatun.
My Bey, when we followed them
they came here.
They moved, obviously.
Osman wouldn't let us go while we had...
...such a treasure as Turgut.
He is capable of doing anything.
You are right, Commander Anselmo.
He can never find us here.
This wound is pierced.
Tell me, how did this wound
happen?
It happened while running away.
When Master Gregor fell.
I've seen many runaways, many injured but
their wounds were not like this.
In the name of Allah, the merciful.
If this Anselmo was Kosses' man...
...then he wouldn't...
...draw his sword to him.
They would draw their sword to both Kosses
and Rogatus.
They are hard to understand.
Then, this Anselmo must have...
...set a trap to Kosses too.
It wasn't for Kosses.
He also tried to take Gregor from Rogatus.
Their only value is gold, brother.
They are dogs for whoever gives
their coin.
But soon, I will expose all their games
one by one.
I hope.
Can we enter, my Bey?
Come in, Saltuk.
My Bey, Father Gregor is wounded.
He doesn't look good.
How is Father Gregor?
There is a wound on his arm, my Bey.
It's like a deep hollow.
How is it now?
I put ointment on it. His wound will heal
but...
...I've seen many accidents, many wounded
people but never a wound like this.
It neither looks like a dagger wound nor
a sword wound.
So, it's not a cut you say?
Could it be an animal attack?
There were no teeth marks either.
It looks carved.
Carved, huh?
Are you feeling better, Father Gregor?
Get well soon.
I am better. Thank you, Osman Bey.
Kumral Abdal is a skilled healer.
He sure will heal you.
Don't worry.
Your life is under our protection.
Please continue to rest.
Hatuns, you didn't turn me down and come.
Thank you.
Thank you, Mahur Hatun.
We had a few problems at first.
But we managed, thankfully.
What I want from you is to show the skills
of Kızılbey Hatuns to everyone.
If people like these rugs, it will be good
for our trade and our tribe.
I have absolute trust in you.
Don't disappoint me.
Come on, good luck.
Thank you, Mahur Hatun.
Whose dog are you?
Why are you standing there?
Speak, heretic!
Speak.
I won't forget this face.
You will pay for this, for sure.
I won't forget.
Everyone is after you, Turgut.
People love you.
However...
... the one that has more money will
get you...
... not the one that loves you more.
Turgut!
I wonder how many of these you are worth.
Do you think they were cheap, Turgut?
No, no.
If my name is Turgut Bey, I will make you
swallow those coins with their bag.
I will send you to hell with them.
Lord Rogatus is coming.
Looks like you had a hard time trying to
find us, Lord Rogatus.
You are a simple man, Anselmo.
Both guessing you would move and sending
someone after you was easy.
Look at this, look!
What is this?
Dirt.
My priceless cape is covered in dirt.
Why though?
I knew this would happen.
But why do I come here anyway?
What do you think?
Anselmo is sorry about this. My men will
clean it at once.
So, Turgut is valuable enough to cover
your nice clothes in the dirt.
Right now, I should have been in
my castle.
Turgut should've been with me and
my clothes should've been clean.
Why is Turgut here?
Why did you bring him here?
Because I think I accepted less than
his worth, Lord Rogatus.
Therefore, I am keeping Turgut.
I get it.
Diego.
Bring Turgut.
He is a noble man...
...is always loyal to his promise.
You owe that purse of gold to this.
Get yourself some clothes with them.
You dress terribly.
I want this great news to Osman Bey
in person.
Can we enter, my Bey?
Come in.
My Bey, Rogatus the Lord of Bilecik is
here to see you.
I will keep it short, Osman Bey.
You told me you didn't know where
Father Gregor was although he was here.
Now, we both know the truth.
You said you would keep it short.
Tell me.
Our terms are equal now.
I didn't come here empty-handed to
take my friend Gregor.
I have something that is valuable for you.
Turgut.
If Turgut is important to you as much as
I heard...
...you will bring Father Gregor to Çakırcı
at noon, tomorrow.
He is not important to me.
He will die if you don't come.
So, it was Rogatus all along.
They took Turgut to give to him.
Gather the beys.
We will discuss this.
As you command, my Bey.
Harmankaya Castle
Tell me, Bahadır.
What news did you bring to us from
the Kayı Tribe?
Does Osman have Turgut or not?
No, he doesn't.
Osman Bey couldn't get Turgut.
Don't worry.
He will get him eventually.
What does that meanü Lord Kosses?
Since Turgut isn't with Osman...
...he is with Anselmo...
... who sold me out to Rogatus.
Then Roga--
In this case, Rogatus will give Turgut and
take Gregor.
If this happens...
...my reputation in King's head will be
terribly hurt, Mari.
Terribly.
If you give Father Gregor and take Turgut,
your people will say that...
... you are showing weakness.
If you don't, a Turkmen Bey will be
held captive by the infidel...
...and you will violate the tradition.
You are right, my Sheik.
Either way is not suitable.
This is a bad situation.
While Sultan Izzettin was a prisoner in
the Byzantine dungeons didn't Berke Han...
... send an army for him from across
the seas, from the Crimea to Byzantium?
Sure. To him, my master Sarı Saltuk
told...
... to follow the tradition.
The Turkish Sultan will not be a prisoner,
he said.
This is a bad situation.
To show weakness in the eyes of the enemy
or...
... to leave a Turkmen Bey to the enemy's
hands.
It is a tough choice.
There is no easy for us, my Sheik.
There is no easy for us.
We testify that you are with Allah,
Osman Bey.
Those who are with Allah always
struggle.
What does it say in the book?
In the Surah Inshirah.
In the name of Allah, the merciful.
Almighty Allah says...
...''In the name of Allah, the merciful.''
''Didn't we open up your heart?''
''Didn't we remove the weight that
bent your back?''
''Have we not exalted your glory?''
So with hardship, there is ease.
Yes.
Every hardship comes with ease.
So when you have finished,
get up and turn only to your Rabb.
Amen, my Sheik.
Amen.
I hope...
... I will follow the tradition and
take Turgut back...
... and I will not leave Father Gregor
to them.
I hope, Osman Bey.
I hope.
Let alone asking how,
I am not even curious.
We know that some works of the Beys are
secret.
No way, my Sheik.
As always, you enlightened us with
your beautiful words.
You gave us a calm breath.
May Allah be pleased with you.
Peace of mind, my Bey.
Peace of mind.
It exactly means what you have said
in Turkish.
Good job.
You have a guest, Bala.
Welcome, Mari.
Thank you, Bala Hatun.
You came to see the rugs, I believe.
-The rugs are here, Here you go.
-Before that...
...I'd like to talk to you about something
important.
Yes, Mari?
What is this, Mari?
The dagger that I gave to
Turgut's scabbard.
Turgut Bey?
Yesterday...
...I helped Turgut running away.
This scabbard is of the dagger I gave him.
He got away thanks to me.
Why?
I wanted to give Turgut to you
but I couldn't.
I wanted you to know that.
By the way...
...I'd be glad if you conveyed what I told
to Osman Bey too.
Thank you, Mari.
Don't worry.
I will tell Osman Bey.
Come on, let's take a look at the rugs.
You seem well, Father Gregor.
Do you have any pain?
Thank you, Osman Bey. I don't have much
pain left.
I believe my wound is healing quickly.
If you are feeling well,
then you can get ready.
You are going to Rogatus.
What?
How did this happen, Andreas?
Did I miss something while
I was unconscious?
Everything was the same, Master Gregor.
This is Lord Rogatus' doing, obviously.
Obviously.
What matters is that we are getting out of
this hell, Master.
Beautiful.
It's like a painting.
Our Hatuns did it.
It's doesn't bleed colors, it
doesn't blench.
They did it with their own hands.
Bala Hatun, I want your rugs in
Harmankaya Palace.
With pleasure.
We should think of every possibility.
I don't want any trouble.
We have warned the soldiers, sir.
Osman...
will try to trick us even he gives
us Gregor back.
Be careful.
After we take Gregor, when we go
back to the castle...
we will use the oldest route.
It will protect us from possible traps.
The place we will meet in matters too.
Choose your best men, place them around.
- Just in case.
- Your command.
He won't take Gregor...
whatever he does.
I'm grateful that you kept your word.
I hope that our friendship
will be honored one day.
Allah knows, Rogatus.
Maybe, one day.
Come on.
Are you okay, Turgut Bey?
Are you hurt?
Come on.
Let's go to the tent, Kumral Abdal will
take care of you.
Bring Turgut Bey's horse.
Thank you, Osman Bey.
I owe you a life.
Thank you.
However...
don't interfere with my business anymore.
I don't want any help from you.
My tent is mine, your
tent is yours.
Your enemy bothers you, my enemy
bothers me.
Don't go into my way anymore, Osman Bey.
How dare you!
We have to cut his tongue.
All the suffering...
Our Bey tried so hard to get the Priest.
Now, for a rebellious Bey...
You will settle down, Turgut Bey.
You only burn where you touch now.
When your fire stops...
When you stop...
then we will be together.
Rogatus, may God bless you.
May God's love always be with you.
Thanks to you, I'm here.
Don't think about these things.
You're already tired.
Have a rest, please. We have lots
of time to talk.
Your arm..
- Did Osman do something bad?
- It's not important.
It's just an accident.
- Welcome, our Bey!
- Thank you.
Thank you.
Welcome, my Bey.
Are you okay, my Bey? How did Nikola
let you go?
Forget about me. How's my tent?
We're fine.
You did a good job.
- Thank you, Kutay.
- Thanks to Osman Bey...
he didn't leave us alone.
How did you come here?
It's complicated.
Osman Bey tried hard.
Thanks to him. He's a brave man.
Don't forget, Kutay.
If Osman Bey didn't withdraw us, none of
it would happen.
It's time for revenge.
Nikola...
Kosses...
We will kill them all.
- My Bey.
- We will.
We will take revenge for what happened,
We won't sleep until we will.
Don't forget that.
(She sings a lullaby)
"May the tent be with you."
"May your food be sweet."
Sleep, my son, sleep.
I see, you don't
want to sleep.
Gökçe, who do you
think did it?
I don't know, Malhun Hatun.
Put Osman to the bed.
Your face...
was different when Bala Hatun
said something.
I don't understand, Malhun Hatun.
What are you doing, Malhun Hatun?
What's it that, Gökçe?
What's that!
You did it, right?
Malhun Hatun, I---
Swear you won't do something
like that again!
Go away! I don't
want to see you.
I will tell you something.
Is it something bad, my Bey?
Be patient.
What will you tell, Osman Bey?
I will tell you something.
When?
When the time comes, you will see.
If anyone wants to leave, he can.
The way is ready.
Whoever wants to come, can come anytime.
Your place is ready.
This is it.
Can I come in, my Bey?
Come in.
Welcome, Priest.
Sleep well now.
We will talk tomorrow.
I don't have anything to talk to you!
Let them end my captivity.
We won't draw a sword unless
it's for protecting you, Priest.
If I were you, I'd pray for this captivity
to continue.
As you won't be safe anywhere
other than here.
Rogatus is my friend.
He is loyal to Jesus.
This world is a lie.
It is, Priest.
Now go rest.
We will talk tomorrow.
Is it good, my Bey?
Yes.
The Priest...
chose us over them.
He chose our shields.
He knows that...
the truth is with us.
And we'll host him.
Your command, my Bey.
We will host him.
Thank you.
You can leave.
Brother.
You stay.
I want to tell you first.
I have never seen a
wound like that before.
It doesn't look like anything.
It looks different. It's like it is
ripped off to put something in.
To put something in...
Kumral Abdal is skillful.
He will cure you.
Don't worry.
Your life is our trust.
You can rest.
Listen to me carefully.
Priest Gregor hides something in his tent.
It seems important.
So important to shed blood.
It is inside the Bible.
Go and take it secretly.
An replace it with this.
- He should know who has done it.
- Your command, my Bey.
You thought it well, brother.
However...
Osman...
what is this?
I don't know, brother.
For now.
However, as he comes back for it...
and he is keeping it under his skin...
it must be important.
We'll see.
He hides it inside his wound, he
comes back for it.
It must be really important.
If it's important for Priest...
it sure is for the others as well.
If it matters for the others
as well, you know...
They may attack us.
I know, brother.
However, I won't give up.
If they attack us...
then I will bury them all...
and I will wash their graves
with their own blood.
Jesus Christ..
I just wish my mind tricked me.
I can't believe we came
back this hell again...
With our own feet!
What you protect is protected by us.
Don't worry.
Osman.
Sir Gregor.
We were protecting it...
and you were almost killed
just to protect it.
I don't understand.
Osman...
how can he know?
It doesn't matter, Andreas.
It belongs to Osman now.
If we leave here...
we may lose it forever.
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com